Prabhat Pareek

C

+917038286618



prabhatpareek91@gmail.com



Noida / Uttar Pradesh / India

2

linkedin.com/in/prabhat-pareek/

SKILLS

7 / 10

MS Office

8/10

Jira, Jile, DevPlus, Prime

4 / 10

SQL

6/10

SAP GTS

6/10

Katalon

EDUCATION

MBA & PGPM - 8.25 CGPA

IBS - Pune

2014 - 2016

B.tech - 69%

Rajasthan Technical University 2009 - 2013

OTHERS

Volunteer

Robin Hood Army – NCR 2017 - Present Bhumi – Pune, NCR 2014 - 2017

ABOUT ME

Business Analyst with 5 years of experience in handling product, supporting business solution software and analyzing business operations.

Aiming to utilize strong experience in agile development methodology (PSPO 1 Certified) and analytical ability to achieve the objective of organization.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Experience in Agile software development methodology
- Handling end to end product delivery
- Worked on various complex deliverables which support critical business driven reports
- Experience in product implementation and maintenance
- Extensive experience of functional and regression testing
- Experience in handling of different clients of different technologies and ERP (SAP)
- Working as Agile change agent
- Identification and tracking of KPIs

EXPERIENCE

Business Analyst

TCS / Noida / Sep 2017 - Present

Domain – Finance (Bespoke application for project Accounting and Invoicing)

Responsibilities

- Gather business requirements form product owner
- Analyze requirements and processes through User Stories
- Conduct release and sprint planning to discuss and estimate requirement
- Conduct testing to verify that DoD is fulfilled
- Provide input into developing and modifying systems to meet client needs and develop business specifications to support these modifications
- Frequent demo and sprint review with business users and stakeholders
- Liaise between business and technical personnel to ensure a mutual understanding of processes and applications
- Impact Analysis of changes to be implemented Automation of reports for analytics purposes

Functional Consultant

TCS / Noida / July 2016 - Aug 2017

Domain - Manufacturing & Aerospace

Responsibilities

- Analyze client's business requirements and processes through BRD and documents
- Configuration of product classification which includes maintaining of Commodity Codes and Export Control Classification
- Configuration and Implementation of Sanctioned Party List (SPL), Embargo and Preference processing
- Managing and processing of License Determination and Legal Control Block
- Prepare test cases and test plan
- Perform unit testing, functional testing and system testing